

CURRICULUM VITAE

NGUYEN VAN MINH

Software Engineer

: 12 December, 1997

⊠: ngxvanminh@gmail.com

2: 0908 120 803

EDUCATION

08/2015 - 07/2019

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology and Education

Major: Electrical & Electronics Engineering

GPA: 7.4

CERTIFICATES

Application of Revit MEP to setup shop drawing of M&E system

ABOUT ME

I'm interested in developing systems and always excited to learn new technology to apply in my project. My strengths are logical thinking, programming, teamwork skill and self study

In 5 years, I hope to advance in my role as much as possible. I enjoy to code and think it is the right choice for me long term. I want to continue working in a professional environment where every employee can improve

SUMMARY INFORMATION

https://www.linkedin.com/in/minhngx

- Experience in programing C/C++ in embedded system
- Experience in programing SQL, Python about Data Science
- Strong technical in PLC programing
- Technical Skills:
 - Tools: AutoCAD, Proteus, LabVIEW
 - Languages: C/C++, Python, SQL, HTML/CSS
 - Framework: tensorflow, pandas, matplotlib, seaborn, sklearn, opencv, selenium
 - Microsoft Office: Excel, Power BI, Visio, SharePoint
 - Git (https://minhngx.github.io)

WORK EXPERIENCE

04/2021 – now	Bosch Global Software Technologies Viet Nam Position: Embedded Software Engineer
	 Tasks: Veryfying the automotive software configuration at Unit test for Active Safety (ABS, EPS) to coverage code Understanding code flow, writing script tests for every complex situation Reporting the real deviation and making a discussion with customers to deal with these issues Compiling documents to improve job productivity, also as training materials Knowledge of black-box and white-box testing
12/2019 - 03/2021	<pre>Intel Products Vietnam Position: Process & Equipment Engineer</pre>
	 Tasks: Repairing and sustaining motherboard of chipsets, SOC and CPU, conducting follow-ups with technicians to ensure minimal issues for motherboard Using SQL, JMP and Python script to monitor and visualize the process to detect signals and maintain it within control Monitoring equipment and process indicators to reduce process variability Coordinating, implementing and developing equipment and process improvements in regards to safety, quality and efficiency by applying 8D, FMEA, MBPS, 5 whys

PROJECTS

Product checking system by LabVIEW - HCMUTE

Final Thesis

⇔ https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nrMJN-T33D8

The project detects 3 common errors in industry. Error signals are connected to the web for easy observe and control

LabVIEW, Siemens, HTML/CSS, Modbus, Web server, Computer Vision

Face Recognition - Minh Nguyen

Project Owner

⇔ https://github.com/minhngx/face_detection

The project simple face regognition tool, which combine Conputer Vision and Face Embedded

Python, SQL, numpy, OpenCV